{
    "subject": "Chelsea_Noble",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Kirk_Cameron",
    "human_readable": "Chelsea Noble is married to Kirk Cameron.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9867804646492004,
            "question": "Is there a known marriage between Chelsea Noble and Kirk Cameron?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9091079235076904,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Chelsea Noble and Kirk Cameron?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9005107283592224,
            "question": "Who is Chelsea Noble married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.887686550617218,
            "question": "Are Kirk Cameron and Chelsea Noble in a romantic relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.885652482509613,
            "question": "Is Kirk Cameron married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8540107607841492,
            "question": "Who are Chelsea Noble and Kirk Cameron?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8174644112586975,
            "question": "To whom is Chelsea Noble wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7768378257751465,
            "question": "Who is Chelsea Noble's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6706390380859375,
            "question": "What is the name of Kirk Cameron's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6683000326156616,
            "question": "What is the name of Kirk Cameron's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chelsea Noble is married to Kirk Cameron.",
            "html": "yago_5287_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Kirk Cameron's wife?",
            "html": "yago_5287_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Chelsea Noble's husband?",
            "html": "yago_5287_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Chelsea Noble wed?",
            "html": "yago_5287_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5287_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5287_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5287_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5287_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5287_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5287_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5287_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5287_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5287_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5287_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I found that:\n\n* Chelsea Noble's full name is indeed Nancy Mueller, but she is best known as Kirk Cameron's wife (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_5287/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt).\n* The couple has six children together, although it is mentioned that they also have two biological children (Olivia Rose and James Thomas) in addition to their other four children (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_5287/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt).\n\nTherefore, the information supports the triple:\n\n\"Chelsea Noble is married to Kirk Cameron.\"\n\nHere is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that Chelsea Noble is married to Kirk Cameron, confirming the statement as correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}